All the rules are broken.
Times have really changed.
Changed my ass.
Some things never change.
What are you afraid of?
We've got people up top protecting us.
We always manage to dodge the bullet, right?
We don't even know who's protecting us.
Now that Guanhong went down,
who's gonna look out for us?
He can't see a thing anymore.
He should've retired a long time ago.
Times are changing too fast.
Is there still a place for us in Gangcheng?
The people backing us only want money.
Not Xie Guanhong.
Anyone else would be the same.
It's not that Gangcheng has no place for us.
We're the ones who chickened out.
Who's there?
Xie Guanhong, you have the nerve to show up?
How did Heyisheng end up with scum like you?
We treated you like a brother.
What do you take us for?
Stabbing us in the back like this?
Playing such a dangerous game.
What do we do now?
How are you gonna clean this up?
Keep your voices down!
Get too worked up and you'll all meet your maker!
You're the biggest bastard of all!
The cops are outside.
You called the cops!
You sold us out from the very start, didn't you?
Are you crazy?!
Are you dragging us down to die with you?
Even if I die today, I'll kill you first!
Calm down!
If you make a move now, the cops will see!
I think we'd better get out of here.
This is a trap.
Yeah.
We really screwed up this time.
Shut up!
I didn't bring the cops here.
I didn't sell out Heyisheng.
I can give up being the Dragon Head,
and I don't even need the Dragon Head Baton.
But we brothers must stand united!
And point our guns at the enemy!
At the enemy?
The cops are right outside!
I don't even have a piece!
Fight them my ass!
In this world,
there's nothing money and guns can't solve.
Either
we stay trapped in a cage like that bird,
or we fight our way out head-on!
A man dies, but his name lives on.
And earn our last shred of dignity.
Be a man, or be a bird...
Or be a bird-man.
You choose.
Everyone, get ready.
Three, two, one.
What are you doing?
I'm the Commander!
Remember, you're a cop.
And your brother's death...
I didn't want it to happen!
Don't bring up my brother!
My brother died in your Anti-Triad Unit.
Isn't that right?!
Move out!
If I'd known it'd come to this, I would've retired long ago.
To think Old Blind Man
would actually get his hands on the Dragon Head Baton.
It's finally in my hands.
Get down!
Go!
Hurry, get upstairs!
Dad!
Dad, what's wrong?
What's wrong, Dad?
What happened?
Answer me!
Dad, what's going on outside?
What the hell is going on?
Dad!
Why do you have a gun?
You can't kill anyone else!
You really can't kill anyone else, Dad!
Cherish the time you have left.
Trust me.
Spread out!
Three
Two
One
Move!
The suspect has a hostage.
Don't do anything rash.
I'll be right there.
Xie Guanhong!
Go!
Dad!
You murderer!
Let him go!